ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Video Bulletin #1: VFW/SEUI Organizing Drive, Community Services Conference, Legislative Report "Unemployment Up and I'm Down" by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 49)
  VHS; 45 min.; Labor Institute of Public Affairs
- Labor Video Bulletin #2: "Molders Magic Chef Strike," CIPA: A Voice for Labor in the Electronic Media by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 50)
  VHS; 30 min.; Labor Institute of Public Affairs
- An Idea Whose Time Has Come. US Dept of Commerce (Box 57, Folder 51)
  VHS; 12.5 min.
- Sik, C., Sol Chaikin - Summer Semester, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 52)
  May; VHS
- Sol Goldberg - Focus on NJ (Box 57, Folder 53)
- Garment Industry Protests Imports Ten Oclock News WNEW-TV. (Box 57, Folder 54)
  VHS; 10 min.; WNEW; June 17
- Sol Chaikin Undocumented Workers, Live at Five WCBS (Box 57, Folder 55)
  VHS: 120 min.; TV WCBS
- "Union Maids," "Jewish Anarchists" (Box 57, Folder 56)
  VHS; WNET; (G. Tyler).
- Labor Video Bulletin #5: Labor's Learning Center; Local TV Spots for Labor; Excerpt from "Inside your Schools" by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs (Box 57, Folder 57)
  VHS; 30 min.
- Sol Chaikin Interview, "The Market Today" FNN., 1983 (Box 57, Folder 58)
  VHS; 120 min.; August 15, 1983
- "Labor Looks at the Eighties Featuring Sol Chaikin of the ILGWU" (Box 57, Folder 300)
  The Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, Inc. Presents
- Union Label Commercials. Crafted with Pride in the USA Council; Crafted with Pride 1987 Commercials; "Pocketbook Patriotism," 6PM News WTMJ. (Box 57, Folder 300a)
- Japan vs. USA: Hi-Tech Shootout, WNBC-TV. (Box 57, Folder 301)
  3/4" U-Matic; August 14
- Local 23-25 Rally [Chinatown]., 1982 (Box 57, Folder 302)
  3/4" U-Matic; 60 min.; June 24, 1982
- Unity House, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 302a)
  3/4" U-Matic and Betacam SP; 32 min.
- Unity House, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 302b)
  3/4" U-Matic andn VHS; 25 min.
- Harris Zinn - "Straight Talk", 1979 (Box 57, Folder 303)
  July 13; WOR TV
- Political Conference, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 304)
  May 5; Cox Cable News
- ILGWU Reel #1 of 2 with Visual Readout, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 305)
  September 13; Teleconcepts.[Convention, 1983]
- ILGWU Reel #2 of 2 with Visual Readout, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 306)
- ILGWU Master Reel (1and2) with Visual Readout, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 307)
  September 13; Teleconcepts; [Convention, 1983]
- Roll-back Imports rally and 34th street march, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 308)
  April 28; outside Macy's (Herald Square); Sol Chaikin speaks
- "ILGWU Rally" With Visual Readout, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 308b)
  April 27; Testimonials by protestors; Chaikin speaks; picture quits periodically
- ILGWU Videoconference Part III, Reel 1, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 309)
  April 23; End of Rally at Herald Square, additional ILGWU interviews and testimonials. May return to the Teleconference
- ILGWU - Reel 1. Interview with Irma Davies; Five other interviews, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 310)
  April 19; on the National Mall in Washington, DC;, 3 African American women, two white women; Original Evelyn Dubrow and Tip O'Neill addresses; Other government official; WETA
- ILGWU - Reel 2 WETA, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 311)
  April 19
- ILGWU cassette #1 Part 1, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 312)
  April 23; Chaikin says the over-riding problems are imports and general non-union competition. Takes questions from Local leaders
- ILGWU cassette #2 Part 2, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 313)
  April 23; President Sol Chaikin. Staff meeting continued
- ILGWU cassette #3 Part 1. Interviews with some of the same people from v310, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 314)
  April 23; Beginning of national teleconference. Features Edward B. Shils, PhD, from the Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers Association
- ILGWU cassette #4 Part 2, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 315)
  April 2; Teleconference continued, with Lane Kirkland, President AFL-CIO, Evelyn Dubrow, Tip O'Neill, Sol Chaikin takes phone calls
- Garment Workers Union Rally, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 316)
  April 23; NBC, ABC, CBS, PIX, CNN. Radio TV Reports, Inc.
- Immigrant Sweatshop Workers in Union City, NJ, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 317)
  November 19; WNEW-TV
- ILGWU Fall River Reel 1, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 318)
  April 12; Teleconcepts
- ILGWU, Mos O'Neill, Tsongas (Box 59, Folder 319)
- Rally - Herald Square, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 320)
  April 23; Teleconcepts
- ILGWU Fall River Reel 2, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 321)
- ILGWU - Master Clip Reel #3, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 322)
  April 21; Show Master
- ILGWU - Master Clip Reel #2, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 323)
  April 21; Teleconcepts.
- ILGWU - Leadered Cuts, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 324)
- "Map of USA" ILGWU 1 production materials, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 325)
- Look for the Union Label, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 326)
  1" magnetic reel; Audio master; Audio cassette transferred to 1"; May 20, 1983
- Sol Chaikin, Reel #2, ILGWU, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 327)
  1" reel; April 23, 1983
- Two/Two for the Union. ILGWU, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 328)
  1" reel; 1.5 min.; May 19, 1983
- ILGWU - "Look for the Union Label", 1983 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  May 18; (2 Copies and 1 original of Enclosed List)
- ILGWU copy - leadered cuts made from video master #5780 73-24 (Box 60, Folder 329b)
- "Look for the Union Label" made from video master #5780 73-24 on February 23, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 329c)
- ILGWU Protest Telconcepts, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 330)
  April 20
- Open/Elenet Unmixed Audio, VT#19, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 331)
- ILGWU Reel 1 Part 1 - Sol Chaikin, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 332)
  April 23
- ILGWU Reel 6 Part 2 - Sol Chaikin, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 333)
- ILGWU Reel 3 Part 1 - Sol Chaikin, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 334)
- ILGWU Reel 4 Part 2 - Sol Chaikin, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 335)
- ILGWU Reel 5 Part 1 - Sol Chaikin, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 336)
- ILGWU Protest March KDKA-TV, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 337)
- Garment Workers Union Rally - NBC, ABC, CBS (Box 61, Folder 338)
- Somma Mattress Strike; Los Angeles, California, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 59)
  September; VHS
- Import Rally, Harrisburg, PA, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 60)
  April 10; VHS
- Gerber - Advanced Technology for the Apparel Industry (Box 62, Folder 61)
- Gerber - Advanced Technology for the Apparel Industry (Box 62, Folder 62)
- Economics U$A; Program 24 (Box 62, Folder 63)
  Labor and Management; PBS 122; VHS
- "Triangle Fire and Interview with Leon Stein" by Sheridan Elson, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 64)
  May 27; VHS
- Reagan: The Rhetoric and the Reality, CWA (Box 62, Folder 65)
- "Pinnacle," ILGWU (Box 62, Folder 66)
- Women in the ILGWU, Evelyn (Evy) Dubrow Roast, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 67)
  February 27; VHS
- Eddie Gonzalez. Last in a series of Public Speaking Courses for 35 Hispanic women in the ILGWU, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 68a)
  October; VHS
- Campaign for America's Future - "Stand with us, America.", 1984 (Box 62, Folder 339)
  September; long commercial for labor movement
- TV's Bloopers and Practical Jokes; Commercial Segment: "Jingles." (Box 62, Folder 340)
- The Willmar 8., 1985 (Box 62, Folder 341)
  September 17; Eight female bank employees in Willmar, MN strike to receive equal pay. Narrated by Lee Green. Aired on PBS, WNET- Newark, NJ
- Crafted with Pride in USA; "Cathy," "Diahann, "O.J", 1985 (Box 62, Folder 342)
  July 22; Union Label commercials; James Caan at the end of each cut; Warwick Advertising
- Crafted with Pride in USA; "Cathy," "Diahann, "O.J", 1985 (Box 62, Folder 343)
  July 25; Union label commercials; Horn/Eisenberg; James Caan at the end of each cut
- Portrait of America, "Connecticut." (Box 62, Folder 344a)
- Sol Chaikin - "Daybreak" - CBS, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 344b)
  November 20; (TV spots, imports, labors' problems)
- Jael and Minute Joshove 1961-1962 (Box 63)
- ILGWU Local 91-105 Education Department, 1989 (Box 63a)
  September 28
- Man of the Sky, 1963 (Box 63b)
  December 26
- Local 91 50th Year, 1985 (Box 63c)
  April
- Fall and Winter Fashion 1961-1962 (Box 63d)
- Fall and Winter Fashion 1961-1962; Fashions USA (Box 63e)
- 1950 ILGWU Jubilee Convention; Print #13, 1964 (Box 64)
  January 27
- The Stevenson Story The Pursuit of Happiness, 1964 (Box 64a)
  January 28; Democratic Political Film; Democratic Committee for Arts
- Fashion Picture, 1960 (Box 65)
  Spring
- S and S 1961 [Spring and Summer Fashions?] (Box 65a)
- S and S 1962 [Spring and Summer Fashions?] (Box 65b)
- S and S 1962 [Spring and Summer Fashions?] (Box 65c)
- 1950 ILGWU Jubilee Convention, 1964 (Box 65d)
  January 3; print #2
- 1950 ILGWU Jubilee Convention, 1964 (Box 65e)
  January 27; print #10 TV
- My Name is Mary Brown (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66a, Folder 39C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66b, Folder 4C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66c, Folder 22C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66d, Folder 15C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66e, Folder 18C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes Ladies Dresses; Union Garment (Box 66f, Folder 20C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66g, Folder 26C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66h, Folder 27C)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 66I, Folder 30C)
- City of Hope (Box 67)
- Before the Day, 1963 (Box 67a)
  May 22
- AFL-CIO Convention 1961; Miami, Florida, 1963 (Box 67b)
- Human Reproduction, 1963 (Box 67c)
- Looking Ahead (Social Security), 1963 (Box 67d)
- Of Human Rights, 1963 (Box 67e)
- Eric R.B, 1969 (Box 67f)
- Cast Me Not Off Print #2, 1963 (Box 67g)
- Dues and the Union, 1961 (Box 67h)
- The Coolibah Tree, 1963 (Box 67I)
- Politics is Money COPE Film #2, 1962 (Box 67j)
- Look for the Label, 1964 (Box 68)
- Fashion Picture, 1960 (Box 68a)
- Do It AFL-CIO COPE (Box 68b)
- 1968- Labors Year of Challenge (Box 68c)
- Big Business in Politics, 1962 (Box 68d)
- Good Work for Democracy, 1971 (Box 68e)
- Check-off: The only way to go (Box 68f)
- Fashions USA Spring and Summer Fashions (Box 68g)
- No Title (Box 68h)
- Our Union, 1963 (Box 68I)
  June; Local 91; Print #2
- Rewind- End Born Equal (Box 69)
- With These Hands (Box 69a)
- With These Hands (Box 69b)
- News (Box 69c)
  Title tape torn
- Take-Up (Box 69d)
  16mm
- Marinaretti Di Mondello; Children in Sailors Uniforms, 1940 (Box 70)
- Bill Blass (Box 70a)
- Carol White sewing label (Box 70b)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 70c)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 70d)
- Cut Version With These Hands, 1989 (Box 70e)
  September; Local 91-105
- [No Title] (Box 71a)
- [No Title] (Box 71b)
- [No Title] (Box 71c)
- Marvin Has It Made (Box 71d)
- Who Makes Your Clothes (Box 71e)
- Public Speaking Class, 1982 (Box 71f)
- [No Title] (Box 71)
- American Fashions, 1962-1963 (Box 71g)
  Fall and Spring, 1962-1963
- [No Title] (Box 72)
- Fall and Winter Fashions, 1964 (Box 72a)
- 1958 Dressmakers Strike (Box 72b)
  Part 2 only
- AFL-CIO Sixth Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 72c, Folder 1)
  Copy; Full Track; December 10; San Francisco, CA; 2nd Day AM Session; George Meany Intro to Leon Stein, Past President ILPA
- Interview. Leon with Desmond Wilcox, 1977 (Box 72c, Folder 2)
  March; 1/2 track; 3 3/4 ips
- BBC TV Interview. Miriam, Barbara, Scott and Desmond Wilcox, 1977 (Box 72c, Folder 3)
  1/2 track; 3 3/4 ips; March
- Unknown Reel (Box 72c, Folder 4)
  Film
- The Triangle Fire. As Told by Leon Stein, 1986 (Box 72c, Folder 5)
  Tape Cassette; Silver Spring, MD; 3c
- ILGWU Convention. "On The Move" ILG Chorus, 1989 (Box 72c, Folder 6)
  Hollywood, FL; Tape Cassette
- ILGWU "An American Christmas", 1983 (Box 72c, Folder 7)
  :60 Radio; Okay; Paula Green; November 29; Tape Cassette
- Fall Faculty Meeting. Lecture by Leon Stein, 1980 (Box 72c, Folder 8)
  August 25; Tape Cassette
- ILGWU 98.5 KRZ (Box 72c, Folder 9)
  Tape Cassette; June 26; 2 x 60
- ILGWU WKR2 (Box 72c, Folder 10)
  Tape Cassette; 2 at :60
- Triangle Fire I. Leon Stein (Box 72c, Folder 11)
  Tape Cassette
- Unknown Cassette (Box 72c, Folder 12)
  Tape Cassette; Atlas Films, NYC, NY
- [untitled] (Box 72d)
- Special report #7 (Audition) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  Radio transcription disc
- Labor's Challenge - Story of Organized Labor in the United States (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Frank Edwards for Sam Beyers (Box 73, Folder 3)
  LP record album
- Frank Edwards (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Labor's Challenge (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Let's Live Democracy (Box 73, Folder 6)
- To Secure These Rights (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Frank Edwards (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Frank Edwards (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Frank Edwarrds - News Commentary (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Meet Your Union - ILGWU Local 99 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Women in Industry (parts 1 and 2) (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Women in Industry (parts 3 and 4) (Box 74, Folder 2)
- The Fifth Union Industries' Show (Box 74, Folder 3)
- History of the U.S. Department of Labor (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Samuel Gompers - Man of Labor (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Story of Organized Labor in the United States (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Prime Minister Parri (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Reports on the Labor Front (side 2) (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Reports on the Labor Front (side 1) (Box 74, Folder 9)
- UMBAY - Evening Show (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Hear It Now - Garment Workers Union (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Honorable Angello Corsi, Undersecretary of the Department of Interior (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Luigi Antonini, 1946 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  Radio transcription disc; September 27, 1946
- Stevenson San Francisco, Civil Liberties - WJZ, 8:30-9:00pm (part 1) (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Stevenson San Francisco, Civil Liberties - WJZ, 8:30-9:00pm (part 2) (Box 75, Folder 4)
- ILGWU of October 8, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Dixiecrats Civil Rights Re-broadcast (Box 75, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee; Truman, Jessel, Bette Davis (Box 75, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee; ABC Net; Truman, Jessel, Bette Davis (Box 75, Folder 8)
- ILGWU; ABC Network show, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  Radio transcription disc; October 22, 1952
- Prime Minister Parri of Italy, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  Radio transcription disc; October 10, 1945
- Prime Minister Parri of Italy, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- ILGWU - Los Angeles; Operator 77 - Program 6 (part 2) (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Mr. Fraud - The Right-to-Wreck Man, AFL Department of Education (Box 76, Folder 2)
- David Dubinsky, ILGWU; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Radio transcription disc; May 27, 1940
- David Dubinsky speech - ILGWU; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- David Dubinsky speech - ILGWU; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Governor Lehman, David Dubinsky; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Governor Lehman - ILGWU; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  Radio transcription disc; May 28, 1940
- Governor Lehman's speech, introduction by David Dubinsky; Madison Square Garden, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Luigi Antonini, introduced by Van Montana; Paris, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  Radio transcription disc; October 12, 1946
- Cavalera Rusticana, WEVD, Local 89 show, 1939 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  Radio transcription disc; April 8, 1939
- Luigi Antonini address for May Day 1939 in Boston (Box 76, Folder 11)
  Radio transcription disc; May 1, 1939
- The Golden Needle, starring Dorothy McGuire (side 2 of 2), 1950 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Radio transcription disc; Tuesday, January 17, 1950
- The Golden Needle, starring Dorothy McGuire (side 1 of 2), 1950 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- UMBAY; afternoon show, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  Radio transcription disc; Octover 12, 1954
- UMBAY; afternoon show (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Luigi Antonini, Columbus Day address, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Labor for Victory, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  Radio transcription disc; October 10, 1943
- Senator William Benton, Voice of Local 89, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  Radio transcription disc; May 3, 1952
- Ministro della Difesa on R. Pacciardi; 80th anniversario della morte di G. Mazzini (Box 77, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Los Angeles; Operator 77, program 1-2 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Los Angeles; Operator 77, program 3-4 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Los Angeles; Operator 77, program 5-6 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- U.S. at work (part 3), 1947 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  Radio transcription disc; October 10, 1947
- Luigi Antonini from Rome; Speech by Honorable Guiseppe Saragot, introduction by Honorable Lupis, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  Radio transcription disc; September 20, 1946
- Luigi Antonini from Rome, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  Radio transcription disc; September 13, 1946
- Luigi Antonini from Rome, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  Radio transcription disc; August 30, 1946
- UMBAY - Evening show, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  Radio transcription disc; October 12, 1954
- Luigi Antonini from Paris (part 2), 1946 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  Radio transcription disc; August 24, 1946
- Luigi Antonini from Paris (part 1), 1946 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Treca at Venezuela, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  Radio transcription disc; January 12, 1957
- Luigi Antonini, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  Radio transcription disc; January 19, 1957
- FDR [President Franklin D. Roosevelt] Anti-Polio Drive, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  Radio transcription disc; January 26, 1957
- Eddie Cantor Show, WFDR, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  Radio transcription disc; transcribed to disc September 26, 1949
- David Dubinsky (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Local 91, Harry Greenberg; WEVD, 1935 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  Radio transcription disc; October 23, 1935
- David Dubinsky - Human Interest; afternoon show, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- David Dubinsky - Human Interest; afternoon show (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Syd Slapery - Sports program, 1950 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  Radio transcription disc; January 11, 1950
- United Nations Appeal for Children; Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  Radio transcription disc; April 13, 1948
- Address by Senator Paul Douglas (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Address by Senator Herbert Lehman (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Eric Severoid from London; ILGWU-MFG Russian Relief Benefit, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  Radio transcription disc; January 21, 1945
- U.S. at Work (part 1), 1947 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- U.S. at Work (part 2), 1947 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- David Dubinsky - Political; afternoon show (Box 79, Folder 12)
- David Dubinsky - Political; afternoon show (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Unlabelled (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Senator Hubert Humphrey of National Conference of Labor's League for Political Education (parts 1 and 4) (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Senator Hubert Humphrey of National Conference of Labor's League for Political Education (parts 2 and 5) (Box 80, Folder 2)
- We can win in 1960 (part 6); Senator Hubert Humphrey of National Conference of Labor's League for Political Education (part 3) (Box 80, Folder 3)
- The Northeast Sings, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- The Northeast Sings, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- The Northeast Sings, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- The Northast Sings, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- this box was removed, it had a few cassettes, which are now in the media case, and the other two items are now in box 157 (Box 81)
  - ILGWU Convention, tapes #1-5; Carter at convention, #1-2 (6 hour mode) [moved from box 81], 1980 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Coverage of ILGWU Chorus rehearsal; WTOP Radio (CBS), 1977 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; Chaikin also singing; Washington, D.C., December 15, 1977
  - Horizons series, National Public Radio; "Battle in the Sweatshops", 1980 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; broadcast March 19, 1980; reporter/producer: Leslie Breeding
  - Hearing on S-680, the Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Crafted With Pride: A song for America's textile workerrs, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    Record album, incudes letter and newspaper clipping
  - Triangle Fire: 75th anniversary, WBAI News, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    Audiocassette; produced by Kathy Dobie and Amy Goodman
  - ILGWU "Veto" #671 and "Washington Veto" #672, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    Audiocassette; "Veto" :50 pre-recorded, :10 live; "Washington Veto" full :60
- ILGWU Rally, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  VHS; Washington, D.C.; edited 1992; 4 minutes
- Advanced Southern Labor School, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  5" audio reel; Tampa, May 1, 1971
- Histadrut, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  5" audio reel; 1st side, Sol C. Chaikin, Toastmaster; 2nd side, David Gingold address; American Hotel, February 12, 1970; taped by William Arnold
- American Free Trade Union Council for Histadrut Conference, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  5" audio reel; speed 3/75; Part I: Brother Chaikin elected chairman of ATUC, his address; Part II: Brother Chaikin's address, luncheon, National Committee for Labor Israel Annual Convention, 45th anniversary; recorded and edited by William Arnold, Associate Director American Trade Union Council, November 30, 1968
- Labor Press Conference, "American Labor and Israel", 1969 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  7" audio reel; Guest Sol Chaikin, Sunday, January 26, 1969
- this box was full of cassettes, they were all moved to the media case (Box 83)
  - SCC Press Conference, 1983 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    September; Soutgh Africa -AFL-CIO
  - Sol Chaikin - Madrid Conference; JLC National Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    January 19
  - ILGWU Radiot Spots, 1981 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    May 14
  - Koch Endorsement, 1985 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Economic Strategies for the 1980s; What Can Leaders Do? (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - 1981 Centennial Convention; Mr Chaiken, President ILGWU on Resolution #30 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    New York Sheraton Centre Hotel
  - America's the Name (Box 195, Folder 1)
    7 songs on Side 1; 7 songs on Side 2
  - ILGWU Radio Spots, 1981 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Arden House, continued, 1979 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    June 6; Collective Bargaining
  - "Sherrye Henry Program" - "Minimum Wages", 1981 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    January 22; WOR Radio; Guest-Phil Comstock
  - Lane Kirkland's Euology at George Meany's Funeral (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - 13th Constituional Convention - Keynote Speech of George Meany, President, AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    November 15; Shearton Washington Hotel - Washington, D.C.
  - Louisiana Radio Review (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Morning Edition - Imports in Garment Industry (Box 202, Folder 1)
    July 27; WNYC
  - President George Meany's Last Speech to the AFL-CIO (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan America; Business and Labor (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - The Bob Grant Program, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    December2
  - SCC at IUO - Industrial Policy, 1984 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    May 11; New York
  - C. Zimmerman Luncheon, 1981 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    April 4; Chick Chaikin; Hotel Roosevelt
  - Friends of Carter-Hondale Dinner, 1979 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    October 24; Hyatt Regency Hotel
  - Dubrow - Easton Inst., 1972 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    October 7
  - Chick Chaikin (Side A); Histadrut, 1973 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Morning Edition #840507; NC Senate Race (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Arden House, 1979 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    June 6
  - Wilkis-Barre, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    February 8
  - Trade Debate; Strobin WOR Radio, 1983 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Local 190; SC Chaikin; Dress Jr Board, 1982 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Sol C Chaikin - 1984 AFL-CIO Civil Liberties Conference (Side A); Sol Chaikin Q & A - George Meany center for Labor Studies (Side B) (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Chaikin Testimonial Speech, 1983 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    March 24
  - SCC - NY Regional Economists, 1984 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    April 24
  - Allentown, 1982 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    February 9
  - Save Social Security Spots (Box 220, Folder 1)
    AFL-CIO; 30 seconds each spot
  - Allentown, 1982 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - WCBS Radio - "Let's Find Out", 1982 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    December 26, 10:30 p.m.; Sol Chaiken guest; Steven Flanders moderator; Produced by Susan Veatch; 28:45
  - ILIGWU Cooperate Hosues - 21st Birthday Message, 1983 (Box 223, Folder 35)
    June; Sol C Chaikin, Presdient ILGWU
  - 10 ILGWU Radio Spot (Box 224, Folder 36)
    Roughs by Tony Schwartz
- ILGWU "Apparel Jobs Abroad", 1992 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  WCBS-TV Channel 2; 60 Minutes at 7 PM; September 27; Video Cassette; New York, NY